Hans Hofmann
Archives of American Art, Smithsonian Institution
- Correspondence, 1914-1966, undated, Series 1:; (Boxes 1-3; 3.0 linear ft.; Reels 5801-5804)
  - Haynes, M. Lucile, 1963 (Box 2, Reel 5802)
  - Fernand Hazen Éditeur (partially in French), 1955-1956 (Box 2, Reel 5802)
  - Heisler, Harry B., 1959, 1964 (Box 2, Reel 5802)
  - Helmsley-Spear, Inc., 1959-1964 (Box 2, Reel 5802)
  - Hendel, Josef (in German), 1957-1964 (Box 2, Reel 5802)
  - Henri, Florence (in German), 1964 (Box 2, Reel 5802)
  - Hentzen, Alfred (in German), 1960 (Box 2, Reel 5802)
  - Herberg, M.(in German), 1965 (Box 2, Reel 5802)
  - Herma, Hans, 1963 (Box 2, Reel 5802)
  - Hillman, Kay, 1963 (Box 2, Reel 5802)
  - Hodges, Alice, 1962 (Box 2, Reel 5802)
  - Hoenigsberg, Robert and Helga (partially in German), 1963-1965 (Box 2, Reel 5802)
  - Hoffmann, Werner (in German), 1962 (Box 2, Reel 5802)
  - Hofmann Foundation, 1958-1964 (Box 2, Reel 5802)
  - Hofmann, Franziskoi (niece "Bobi") (in German), 1958-1966 (Box 2, Reel 5802)
  - Hofmann, Hans-Theo (nephew) (in German), 1951-1965 (Box 2, Reel 5802)
  - Hofmann, Käthe (sister-in-law) (in German), 1951-1966 (Box 2, Reel 5802)
  - Hofmann, Maria ("Miz") Wolfegg (in German), 1938-1939, undated (Box 2, Reel 5802)
  - Hofmann, Maria ("Miz") Wolfegg, Death-Condolence Letters, A-Z, 1963, (3 folders) (Box 2, Reel 5802)
  - Hofmann, Maria ("Miz") Wolfegg, Death-Floral Tributes, A-Z, 1963 (Box 2, Reel 5802)
  - Hofmann, Maria ("Miz") Wolfegg, Death-Miscellaneous Correspondence and Records, 1963 (Box 2, Reel 5802)
  - Hofmann, Renate Schmitz (See: Schmitz, Renate) (Box 2, Reel 5802)
  - Holiday, 1959 (Box 2, Reel 5802)
  - Hollander Workshop Gallery (See also: Contemporary Portfolios, Inc.), 1965 (Box 2, Reel 5802)
  - Hopkins Center (See: Dartmouth College) (Box 2, Reel 5802)
  - Holst, Bill, 1959 (Box 2, Reel 5802)
  - Huck, Peggy, undated (Box 2, Reel 5802)
  - Hunter, Sam (See: Rose Art Museum, Brandeis University) (Box 2, Reel 5802)
  - Indian Ambassador (See: Ambassador of India) (Box 2, Reel 5802)
  - Illinois Institute of Technology (See: Design Students Association, Institute of Design) (Box 2, Reel 5802)
  - Institute of Contemporary Art, Boston, 1963 (Box 2, Reel 5802)
  - Institute of International Education, 1958 (Box 2, Reel 5802)
  - International Center of Aesthetic Research, 1962-1963 (Box 2, Reel 5802)
  - International Who's Who, 1964 (Box 2, Reel 5802)
  - Ireland, Ben L., 1964 (Box 2, Reel 5802)
  - Iseman, Marjorie (Mrs. Joseph), 1961 (Box 2, Reel 5802)
  - Israel, Alfred, 1965 (Box 2, Reel 5802)
  - Israel Institute of Technology, Inc. (See: American Society for Technion) (Box 2, Reel 5802)
  - It Is Magazine, 1965 (Box 2, Reel 5802)
  - Jackson, Martha, 1964-1965 (Box 2, Reel 5802)
  - Jacobs, Kenneth M., 1962 (Box 2, Reel 5802)
  - Jaffe, Irma B., 1965 (Box 2, Reel 5802)
  - Sidney Janis Gallery, 1963 (Box 2, Reel 5802)
  - Janss, Anne and Bill, 1964 (Box 2, Reel 5802)
  - Jensen, Margaret, undated (Box 2, Reel 5802)
  - Jewell, Edward Alden, 1945 (Box 2, Reel 5802)
  - Johnson, Buffie, 1957-1964 (Box 2, Reel 5802)
  - Johnson, David S., 1963 (Box 2, Reel 5802)
  - Johnston, Maggie, 1965 (Box 2, Reel 5802)
  - Jones, Alfred E., Jr., 1955 (Box 2, Reel 5802)
  - Jones, Bob, 1962 (Box 2, Reel 5802)
  - Journal of Aesthetics and Art Criticism, 1952 (Box 2, Reel 5802)
  - Kanovitz, Howard and Mary, 1965 (Box 2, Reel 5802)
  - Kaprow, Allan, 1957, 1964 (Box 2, Reel 5802)
  - Tizca Karlis Gallery, 1963, 1965 (Box 2, Reel 5802)
  - Kasle, Gertrude, 1964 (Box 2, Reel 5802)
  - Katzen, Lila, 1963 (Box 2, Reel 5802)
  - W. R. Keating & Co., Inc., 1960 (Box 2, Reel 5802)
  - Kelemen, Emil (See: Zilzer, Byula and Emil Kelemen) (Box 2, Reel 5802)
  - Kennedy, Janet, undated (Box 2, Reel 5802)
  - Kepes, Gyorgy, 1963 (Box 2, Reel 5802)
  - Kiesler, Frederick J., undated (Box 2, Reel 5802)
  - Kingsland, James, 1957 (Box 2, Reel 5802)
  - Kinzinger, Edward(in German), 1958 (Box 2, Reel 5802)
  - Knox, Seymour H., 1959 (Box 2, Reel 5802)
  - Koch, Erik and Barbara, 1964 (Box 2, Reel 5802)
  - Koler, Hannah, 1958, 1964 (Box 2, Reel 5802)
  - Samuel M. Kootz Gallery, 1941-1966, undated (Box 2, Reel 5802)
  - Samuel M. Kootz Gallery, cont'd., 1941-1966, undated (Box 2, Reel 5803)
  - Kotin, Albert, 1964 (Box 2, Reel 5803)
  - Krannert Art Museum (See: University of Illinois) (Box 2, Reel 5803)
  - Kuh, Katharine, 1961 (Box 2, Reel 5803)
  - Kunitz, Stanley and Elise Asher, 1963 (Box 2, Reel 5803)
  - Kuper, Rose, 1963 (Box 2, Reel 5803)
  - La Selle, Dorothy Antoinette, 1959-1965 (Box 2, Reel 5803)
  - Lane, William H., 1953-1957, undated (Box 2, Reel 5803)
  - Larsen, Marie (Mrs. Bror), 1962 (Box 2, Reel 5803)
  - Lazarus, Lois, 1957-1958 (Box 2, Reel 5803)
  - Lazarus, Marvin P., 1962, 1964 (Box 2, Reel 5803)
  - Lembach, John, 1964 (Box 2, Reel 5803)
  - Lempertz of Cologne, Inc., 1965 (Box 2, Reel 5803)
  - Leonard, Jack, 1961 (Box 2, Reel 5803)
  - Lescaze, William and Mary, 1956-1964 (Box 2, Reel 5803)
  - Levinson, Jo Ann List, 1964 (Box 2, Reel 5803)
  - Levy, Dr. and Mrs., 1961 (Box 2, Reel 5803)
  - Levy, Rudolph (See: War Compensation) (Box 2, Reel 5803)
  - Lewis, Paul G., 1959 (Box 2, Reel 5803)
  - Life, 1957, 1963 (Box 2, Reel 5803)
  - Abraham Lincoln High School, Brooklyn, 1952 (Box 2, Reel 5803)
  - Linker, Anne, 1947 (Box 2, Reel 5803)
  - Linn, Mr. and Mrs. John, 1960 (Box 2, Reel 5803)
  - A. J. Lipp Litho Co., 1958 (Box 2, Reel 5803)
  - Lister, Jeanne, 1960 (Box 2, Reel 5803)
  - Little, John, 1958 (Box 2, Reel 5803)
  - Loden, Frieda Santz (in German), 1964 (Box 2, Reel 5803)
  - Longview Foundation, Inc., 1958-1963, undated (Box 2, Reel 5803)
  - Look, 1948-1959 (Box 2, Reel 5803)
  - Loran, Erle (See also: University of California, Berkeley-Gifts of Paintings and Museum Wing; University of California, Berkeley-Honorary Degree), 1956-1965, undated (Box 2, Reel 5803)
  - Loriot, G., 1956 (Box 2, Reel 5803)
  - Los Angeles County Museum of Art, 1951, 1965 (Box 2, Reel 5803)
  - Louisiana State University, 1964 (Box 2, Reel 5803)
  - Low, Fritz and Mathilde, 1961-1964 (Box 2, Reel 5803)
  - Lund, Lyle P., 1957-1962 (Box 2, Reel 5803)
  - Lust, Herbert, 1959, 1962 (Box 2, Reel 5803)
  - Macdonald, James W. G., 1949 (Box 2, Reel 5803)
  - Macnaughton, Alan A., 1957, undated (Box 2, Reel 5803)
  - Mademoiselle, 1955-1958 (Box 2, Reel 5803)
  - Maeght Gallery (See: Galerie Maeght) (Box 2, Reel 5803)
  - Magazine of Art, 1952 (Box 2, Reel 5803)
  - Mansfield, Nancy, undated (Box 2, Reel 5803)
  - Massachusetts Registry of Motor Vehicles, 1963 (Box 2, Reel 5803)
  - Mayor's Advisory Committee for the Aged, 1957 (Box 2, Reel 5803)
  - McGraw, Durban A., 1945 (Box 2, Reel 5803)
  - McMullen, Marilyn Earls, 1959 (Box 2, Reel 5803)
  - McNeil, George, 1957-1965 (Box 2, Reel 5803)
  - Megan, Paul J., 1960 (Box 2, Reel 5803)
  - Mercer, Phyllis and George, 1963, 1965 (Box 2, Reel 5803)
  - Messer, Tom and Remi, 1965 (Box 2, Reel 5803)
  - Metro, 1962 (Box 2, Reel 5803)
  - Metropolitan Museum of Art, 1951-1952 (Box 2, Reel 5803)
  - Michaels, Barbara (Mrs. Arthur), 1963 (Box 2, Reel 5803)
  - Milius, Tom, 1941-1945 (Box 2, Reel 5803)
  - Miller, Agnes L. Hood, undated (Box 2, Reel 5803)
  - Miller, Dorothy, 1960, 1962 (Box 2, Reel 5803)
  - Milwaukee Art Institute/Milwaukee Arts Center, 1944-1962 (Box 2, Reel 5803)
  - Minneapolis Institute of Arts, 1961 (Box 2, Reel 5803)
  - Minneapolis School of Art, 1964 (Box 2, Reel 5803)
  - Mnuchin, Leon A., undated (Box 2, Reel 5803)
  - Modern Art Annual, 1950 (Box 2, Reel 5803)
  - Momentum (See: Exhibition Momentum) (Box 2, Reel 5803)
  - Montclair Art Museum, 1952 (Box 2, Reel 5803)
  - Montreal Museum of Fine Arts, 1963 (Box 2, Reel 5803)
  - Morgan, Maude, 1964, undated (Box 2, Reel 5803)
  - Motherwell, Robert and Helen Frankenthaler, 1958-1964 (Box 2, Reel 5803)
  - Moufang, Wilhelm (in German), 1958 (Box 2, Reel 5803)
  - Mueller, Peggy (Mrs. George W. Haldeman), 1957 (Box 2, Reel 5803)
  - Müller, Dody, 1962-1963 (Box 2, Reel 5803)
  - Mundt, Ernest, 1963 (Box 2, Reel 5803)
  - Munson-Williams-Proctor Institute, 1957-1958 (Box 2, Reel 5803)
  - Münter, Gabriele (in German), 1954 (Box 2, Reel 5803)
  - Murchison, Carl and Dorotea, 1965 (Box 2, Reel 5803)
  - Musée des Arts Décoratifs (in French), 1960-1961 (Box 2, Reel 5803)
  - Museum des 20.Jahrhunderts (partially in German), 1961 (Box 2, Reel 5803)
  - Museum of Modern Art (See also: Friends of the Museum of Modern Art Emergency Committee; National Committee on Art Education, Museum of Modern Art), 1951-1966, (3 folders) (Box 2, Reel 5803)
  - Namuth, Hans, 1963-1964 (Box 2, Reel 5803)
  - Napoli, Giuseppe, 1965 (Box 2, Reel 5803)
  - National Association for the Advancement of Colored People, 1964 (Box 2, Reel 5803)
  - National Citizens for Johnson and Humphrey, 1964 (Box 2, Reel 5803)
  - National Committee on Art Education (Museum of Modern Art), 1958 (Box 2, Reel 5803)
  - National Council For U. S. Art, Inc., 1955 (Box 2, Reel 5803)
  - National Institute of Arts and Letters, 1963-1965 (Box 2, Reel 5803)
  - Neff, Wallace, 1965 (Box 2, Reel 5803)
  - William Rockhill Nelson Gallery of Art, 1964 (Box 2, Reel 5803)
  - Neue Galerie im Künstler Haus München (in German), 1962-1963, undated (Box 2, Reel 5803)
  - New England Council for Economic Development, 1958-1959 (Box 2, Reel 5803)
  - New England Telephone, 1963 (Box 2, Reel 5803)
  - New York Clinic for Mental Health Art Sale, 1961 (Box 2, Reel 5803)
  - New York Graphic Society, Inc., 1965 (Box 2, Reel 5803)
  - New York Herald Tribune, 1963 (Box 2, Reel 5803)
  - New York State Council on the Arts, 1951 (Box 2, Reel 5803)
  - New York Studio School, 1965 (Box 2, Reel 5803)
  - New York Telephone Company, 1958 (Box 2, Reel 5803)
  - New York Times, 1964 (Box 2, Reel 5803)
  - New York University, 1957 (Box 2, Reel 5803)
  - Newbill, Al, 1965 (Box 2, Reel 5803)
  - Newman, Barnett, 1965 (Box 2, Reel 5803)
  - Newsweek, 1961, 1964 (Box 2, Reel 5803)
  - Niswanger, Herbert (in German), 1963 (Box 2, Reel 5803)
  - Nordness Gallery, 1962 (Box 2, Reel 5803)
  - Novelli, Anna Maria, 1964 (Box 2, Reel 5803)
  - O'Connor, Elizabeth, 1965 (Box 3, Reel 5803)
  - O'Connor, Francis V., 1964 (Box 3, Reel 5803)
  - Oertly, Alda, 1943-1965 (Box 3, Reel 5803)
  - Ohio Wesleyan University, 1958 (Box 3, Reel 5803)
  - Olsen, Fred H.,1958, 1965 (Box 3, Reel 5803)
  - Oregon State University, 1961 (Box 3, Reel 5803)
  - Otis, Kathryn, undated (Box 3, Reel 5803)
  - Pagán, Evelyn, 1964 (Box 3, Reel 5803)
  - Betty Parsons Gallery, 1947, 1957 (Box 3, Reel 5803)
  - Pataky, Tibor, 1963 (Box 3, Reel 5803)
  - Patnaik, Debra Prasad, 1966 (Box 3, Reel 5803)
  - Pavia, Philip, 1959-1960 (Box 3, Reel 5803)
  - Pennsylvania Academy of the Fine Arts, 1954, 1965 (Box 3, Reel 5803)
  - Person, Dr., undated (Box 3, Reel 5803)
  - Phillips, Marlene, 1960 (Box 3, Reel 5803)
  - Phoenix Art Museum, 1963-1964 (Box 3, Reel 5803)
  - Pictures on Exhibit, 1947 (Box 3, Reel 5803)
  - Pierce, Earl, 1961-1962 (Box 3, Reel 5803)
  - Pittsburgh Board of Public Education, 1947 (Box 3, Reel 5803)
  - Plaskett, Joseph, 1950 (Box 3, Reel 5803)
  - Poindexter, Sterling, 1945-1959 (Box 3, Reel 5803)
  - Pousette-Dart, Nathaniel, 1956, 1963 (Box 3, Reel 5803)
  - Powell, Diane, 1959 (Box 3, Reel 5803)
  - Pratt Institute, 1962, 1965 (Box 3, Reel 5803)
  - Price, Grace Hartigan, 1963-1964 (Box 3, Reel 5803)
  - Project Sigma, 1965 (Box 3, Reel 5803)
  - Provincetown Art Association, 1945-1965 (Box 3, Reel 5803)
  - Provincetown Symphony Orchestra, 1965 (Box 3, Reel 5803)
  - Puma Gallery, 1943, undated (Box 3, Reel 5803)
  - Putzel, Howard and Estelle Putzel (mother), 1944-1945 (Box 3, Reel 5803)
  - Querido, John and Zita, 1960-1965 (Box 3, Reel 5803)
  - Rehbuck, Joseph (in German), 1962-1963 (Box 3, Reel 5803)
  - Reichstmmer der bildenden künste (in German), 1937 (Box 3, Reel 5803)
  - Reiter, Anna, 1957 (Box 3, Reel 5803)
  - Repogle, R. V. (See: Barr, M. G. and R. B. Repogle) (Box 3, Reel 5803)
  - Richter, Hans (in German), 1958 (Box 3, Reel 5803)
  - Richmond Artists Association, 1957 (Box 3, Reel 5803)
  - Riesenfeld, Victor S., 1945 (Box 3, Reel 5803)
  - Riportella, Vincent, 1964 (Box 3, Reel 5803)
  - M. F. Roach Company, 1964 (Box 3, Reel 5803)
  - Robertson, Foster, 1965 (Box 3, Reel 5803)
  - Esther Robles Galley, 1958 (Box 3, Reel 5803)
  - Rogers, Mary, 1959, 1963 (Box 3, Reel 5803)
  - Roh, Franz (in German), 1960, 1962 (Box 3, Reel 5803)
  - Rose Art Museum, Brandeis University, 1962-1964 (Box 3, Reel 5803)
  - Rosenberg, Harold and Maynatalie, 1958-1965, undated (Box 3, Reel 5803)
  - Rosenberg, Patia, 1963-1965 (Box 3, Reel 5803)
  - Rosenman and Colin (See: University of California, Berkeley-Gifts of Paintings and Museum Wing) (Box 3, Reel 5803)
  - Rosenman, Samuel I., 1964 (Box 3, Reel 5803)
  - Rosenthal, Gertrude (See also: Baltimore Museum of Art), 1954-1965 (Box 3, Reel 5803)
  - Rosner, 1962 (Box 3, Reel 5803)
  - Roth, Sydney M., 1963 (Box 3, Reel 5803)
  - Rothschild, Judith, 1963 (Box 3, Reel 5803)
  - Rowohlts Deutsche Enzyklopädie (in German), 1962, 1964 (Box 3, Reel 5803)
  - Rudershausen, Jutta (in German), 1962 (Box 3, Reel 5803)
  - Bertrand Russell Peace Foundation, 1963 (Box 3, Reel 5803)
  - Russi, Gertrude K. (Mrs. Simon), 1962 (Box 3, Reel 5803)
  - Ryder, Cornelia (Mrs. Worth), 1960-1961 (Box 3, Reel 5803)
  - Sachs, Adele, 1958 (Box 3, Reel 5803)
  - Sachs, Edith J., 1958 (Box 3, Reel 5803)
  - Sahl, Hans, 1952-1963 (Box 3, Reel 5803)
  - Saltonstall, Nathaniel, 1964 (Box 3, Reel 5803)
  - Sampson, Atlanta, 1963 (Box 3, Reel 5803)
  - San Antonio Art Institute, 1965 (Box 3, Reel 5803)
  - San Francisco Art Institute, 1962 (Box 3, Reel 5803)
  - San Francisco Museum of Art, 1943-1947 (Box 3, Reel 5803)
  - Santa Barbara Museum of Art, 1959-1964 (Box 3, Reel 5803)
  - Sawyer, Kenneth B., 1960 (Box 3, Reel 5803)
  - Scheier, Edwin and Mary, 1964 (Box 3, Reel 5803)
  - Schlien, Helen (Mrs. John M.), 1964 (Box 3, Reel 5803)
  - Schmailzl, Christine (in German), 1964 (Box 3, Reel 5803)
  - Schitmz, Renate (in German), 1964-1965, undated (Box 3, Reel 5803)
  - Schreyer, Greta, 1958 (Box 3, Reel 5803)
  - Schrier, N. (in German), 1957 (Box 3, Reel 5803)
  - Carl Schurz Memorial Foundation, Inc., 1957 (Box 3, Reel 5803)
  - Clinton W. Schwambe & Co., Inc., 1957-1964 (Box 3, Reel 5803)
  - Seckler, Dorothy Gees, 1960-1966 (Box 3, Reel 5803)
  - Seestaller, Sofie (in German), 1947 (Box 3, Reel 5803)
  - Segui, Shinichi, 1964 (Box 3, Reel 5803)
  - Seitz, William and Irma (See also: Museum of Modern Art), 1952-1965 (Box 3, Reel 5803)
  - Der Senator für Volksbildung (in German), 1962-1963 (Box 3, Reel 5803)
  - Shaier, Mary, 1964 (Box 3, Reel 5803)
  - Shiras, Howard H. (Hoyt), 1958 (Box 3, Reel 5803)
  - Siegel, Florence, 1959 (Box 3, Reel 5803)
  - Siegel, Jeanne, undated (Box 3, Reel 5803)
  - Sigma (See: Project Sigma) (Box 3, Reel 5803)
  - Signa Gallery, 1958 (Box 3, Reel 5803)
  - Silvermine Guild School of Art, 1958 (Box 3, Reel 5803)
  - Simon and Schuster, undated (Box 3, Reel 5803)
  - 67 Gallery (See: Putzel, Howard) (Box 3, Reel 5803)
  - Simpson, Nancy, 1958-1959 (Box 3, Reel 5803)
  - Sles, Stephen, 1957-1964 (Box 3, Reel 5803)
  - Slotnik, Merv, 1964 (Box 3, Reel 5803)
  - Slutsky, Eugene Harvey, 1965 (Box 3, Reel 5803)
  - Smithers, Mary Lou, 1963-1964 (Box 3, Reel 5803)
  - Smithers, Mary Lou, cont'd., 1963-1964 (Box 3, Reel 5804)
  - Snow, A. M., undated (Box 3, Reel 5804)
  - Sofro, Louis J., 1957 (Box 3, Reel 5804)
  - Solinger, David (See also: Hofmann Foundation), 1958-1965 (Box 3, Reel 5804)
  - Souchon, Marion, 1945 (Box 3, Reel 5804)
  - Southern Illinois University, 1958 (Box 3, Reel 5804)
  - Spanish Refugee Aid, Inc., 1960 (Box 3, Reel 5804)
  - Sprinkling, Sondra, 1963 (Box 3, Reel 5804)
  - Städtische Galerie im Lenbachhaus (in German), 1962-1963, undated (Box 3, Reel 5804)
  - State Department (See: Department of State) (Box 3, Reel 5804)
  - State of Louisiana Art Commission, 1962 (Box 3, Reel 5804)
  - State of New York Office for the Aging, 1964 (Box 3, Reel 5804)
  - Staten Island Institute of Arts and Sciences, 1961 (Box 3, Reel 5804)
  - Steinhof, Eugen (See: War Compensation) (Box 3, Reel 5804)
  - Steinman, Anne, 1960, 1963 (Box 3, Reel 5804)
  - Stengel, Walter (in German), 1957 (Box 3, Reel 5804)
  - Stephan, W. H., 1951 (Box 3, Reel 5804)
  - Stern, Rudolf, 1958, 1964 (Box 3, Reel 5804)
  - Stevenson, Beulah, 1954 (Box 3, Reel 5804)
  - Strauss, Willi (in German), 1962-1965 (Box 3, Reel 5804)
  - De Studerendes Rad Kunstakademiets Maier-Og Billedhuggerskoler, 1961 (Box 3, Reel 5804)
  - Sweeney, James Johnson, 1940-1945, undated (Box 3, Reel 5804)
  - Syracuse University, 1956-1966 (Box 3, Reel 5804)
  - Tabachnik, Anne, 1961 (Box 3, Reel 5804)
  - Talbert, Joe, 1961 (Box 3, Reel 5804)
  - Tanager Gallery, 1958 (Box 3, Reel 5804)
  - Terrain Gallery, 1958 (Box 3, Reel 5804)
  - Texas State College for Women, 1944-1945 (Box 3, Reel 5804)
  - Thomas, Charles A., 1964 (Box 3, Reel 5804)
  - Thompson, Kay C. and Alden, 1964-1965 (Box 3, Reel 5804)
  - Thurn, Ernest, 1963 (Box 3, Reel 5804)
  - Time, 1957-1961 (Box 3, Reel 5804)
  - Tougaloo Southern Christian College, 1963-1964 (Box 3, Reel 5804)
  - Town Planning Associates, 1950 (Box 3, Reel 5804)
  - Towson State College, 1965 (Box 3, Reel 5804)
  - Tracy, Lois, 1962 (Box 3, Reel 5804)
  - Trocchi, Alexander, 1964 (Box 3, Reel 5804)
  - Tuchman, Maurice, 1959 (Box 3, Reel 5804)
  - Tworkov, Jack and Wally, 1961-1964 (Box 3, Reel 5804)
  - Tyler, Kenneth, 1966 (Box 3, Reel 5804)
  - United Jewish Appeal of Greater New York, 1965 (Box 3, Reel 5804)
  - University of California, Berkeley, 1964-1965 (Box 3, Reel 5804)
  - University of California, Berkeley-Gifts of Paintings and Museum Wing (See also: Loran, Erle; Wessels, Glenn A. and Kay), 1961-1966 (Box 3, Reel 5804)
  - University of California, Berkeley-Honorary Degree (See also: Loran, Erle; Wessels, Glenn A. and Kay), 1963-1964 (Box 3, Reel 5804)
  - University of California, Los Angeles-Art Gallery (See: Wight, Frederick S.) (Box 3, Reel 5804)
  - University of California Press, 1957 (Box 3, Reel 5804)
  - University of California, San Diego, 1964 (Box 3, Reel 5804)
  - University of Illinois, 1944-1962 (Box 3, Reel 5804)
  - University of Miami, 1961 (Box 3, Reel 5804)
  - University of Michigan, 1958-1963 (Box 3, Reel 5804)
  - University of Minnesota, 1951-1952 (Box 3, Reel 5804)
  - University of Notre Dame, 1963 (Box 3, Reel 5804)
  - University of Southern California, 1963 (Box 3, Reel 5804)
  - University of Texas, 1945 (Box 3, Reel 5804)
  - University of Utah, 1958 (Box 3, Reel 5804)
  - University of Washington, 1961 (Box 3, Reel 5804)
  - Utrecht Linen, 1961 (Box 3, Reel 5804)
  - Van Dyke, Helen B., undated (Box 3, Reel 5804)
  - Van Hoorns, Mary, 1964 (Box 3, Reel 5804)
  - Varady, Suzanne, 1958-1964 (Box 3, Reel 5804)
  - Village Voice, 1958 (Box 3, Reel 5804)
  - Virginia Museum of the Fine Arts, 1962 (Box 3, Reel 5804)
  - Voggenauer, Kate (niece) (in German), 1963-1964 (Box 3, Reel 5804)
  - Vogue, 1957-1965 (Box 3, Reel 5804)
  - Von Guttry, Sophie (in German), undated (Box 3, Reel 5804)
  - Vytlacil, Vaclav, 1963 (Box 3, Reel 5804)
  - WABD (See: Channel 5, WABD) (Box 3, Reel 5804)
  - Wadsworth Athenaeum, 1962 (Box 3, Reel 5804)
  - Walden School, 1958 (Box 3, Reel 5804)
  - Waldman, Paul, 1960 (Box 3, Reel 5804)
  - Walker Art Center, 1951-1961 (Box 3, Reel 5804)
  - Walker, Dr., 1949 (Box 3, Reel 5804)
  - Walker, Hudson D., 1964 (Box 3, Reel 5804)
  - War Compensation (in German and French), 1912-1923 (Box 3, Reel 5804)
  - Ward, Virginia Shaw (Mrs. S. B.), undated (Box 3, Reel 5804)
  - Washington Gallery of Modern Art, 1963-1964 (Box 3, Reel 5804)
  - Washington Square Village (52 West 8th St. apartment), 1958-1965, undated (Box 3, Reel 5804)
  - Watkins Gallery (See: American University) (Box 3, Reel 5804)
  - Watrous, James, 1956 (Box 3, Reel 5804)
  - Weill, Guy A., 1960 (Box 3, Reel 5804)
  - Weinbaum, Judith, 1946 (Box 3, Reel 5804)
  - Weisgal, Fred E., 1965 (Box 3, Reel 5804)
  - Wells, Mason B., 1958-1965, undated (Box 3, Reel 5804)
  - Wessels, Glenn A. and Kay 1964 (See also: University of California, Berkeley-Gifts of Paintings and Museum Wing; University of California, Berkeley-Honorary Degree), 1956-1964 (Box 3, Reel 5804)
  - White House Festival of the Arts, 1965 (Box 3, Reel 5804)
  - John Dickson White Museum of Art (Cornell University), 1959 (Box 3, Reel 5804)
  - Whitney Museum of American Art, 1951-1965, undated (Box 3, Reel 5804)
  - Whitsett, William, 1956 (Box 3, Reel 5804)
  - Wiener, Ingeborg and Paul, 1964 (Box 3, Reel 5804)
  - Wight, Frederick S., 1956-1962 (Box 3, Reel 5804)
  - Willard, Charlotte, 1958-1963 (Box 3, Reel 5804)
  - Williams, Nina S., 1963 (Box 3, Reel 5804)
  - Wilmington Society of the Fine Arts, 1961 (Box 3, Reel 5804)
  - Howard Wise Gallery, 1961 (Box 3, Reel 5804)
  - Witter, Ella, 1963-1964 (Box 3, Reel 5804)
  - WNCN Radio, 1963 (Box 3, Reel 5804)
  - Wolf, Ben, 1963 (Box 3, Reel 5804)
  - Wolsky, Milton, 1966 (Box 3, Reel 5804)
  - Woodard, M. P., 1948 (Box 3, Reel 5804)
  - Writers and Artists Project, 1965 (Box 3, Reel 5804)
  - Württembergischer Kunstverein (in German), 1965 (Box 3, Reel 5804)
  - The Yale Literary Magazine, 1955 (Box 3, Reel 5804)
  - Yale University School of Art and Architecture, 1963 (Box 3, Reel 5804)
  - William H. Young Insurance Company, 1963 (Box 3, Reel 5804)
  - Zilzer, Byula and Emil Kelemen (in German), 1963 (Box 3, Reel 5804)
  - Zogbaum, Wilfred, 1964 (Box 3, Reel 5804)
  - Zwillinger, Vera B., undated (Box 3, Reel 5804)
  - Unknown (A-Z, unsigned and illegible), circa 1934-1965, undated (Box 3, Reel 5804)
    - Bill, 1963 (Box 3, Reel 5804)
    - Dorothy, 1958, 1964 (Box 3, Reel 5804)
    - Dorothy and Roddy, 1965 (Box 3, Reel 5804)
    - Elyn, 1962 (Box 3, Reel 5804)
    - Fifi (See: Brechemin, Louis) (Box 3, Reel 5804)
    - Frank, undated (Box 3, Reel 5804)
    - Fred, undated (Box 3, Reel 5804)
    - Hans, 1965 (Box 3, Reel 5804)
    - Janet, undated (Box 3, Reel 5804)
    - Jenny and Clem, 1964, undated (Box 3, Reel 5804)
    - John, Ella, Jeff, Rodney, 1964, undated (Box 3, Reel 5804)
    - Joy, undated (Box 3, Reel 5804)
    - Joy and Marc, 1963, undated (Box 3, Reel 5804)
    - Katherine, 1934 or earlier (Box 3, Reel 5804)
    - Maria, undated (Box 3, Reel 5804)
    - Mary, 1966 (Box 3, Reel 5804)
    - Mary and Eddie, 1963-1965, undated (Box 3, Reel 5804)
    - Meta, 1958, 1964 (Box 3, Reel 5804)
    - Patricia and Stephen, 1963 (Box 3, Reel 5804)
    - Paul, 1964 (Box 3, Reel 5804)
    - Peter, Vita, Andrea, 1964 (Box 3, Reel 5804)
    - Ronald, 1965 (Box 3, Reel 5804)
    - Trude, 1963 (Box 3, Reel 5804)
    - Unsigned and Illegible, 1944-1965, undated (Box 3, Reel 5804)
- School of Fine Arts Records, 1915-1965, undated, Series 2:; (Boxes 4-5; 2.0 linear ft.; Reels 5804-5806)
  The Hans Hofmann Schule für Bildende Kunst operated in Munich from 1915-1933. The very sparse extant records are small amount of printed matter and a financial document. The Hans Hofmann School of Fine Arts, was established in New York in 1933, and his summer school in Provincetown, Massachusetts, opened in 1934. Both closed in 1958, because after 43 consecutive years of teaching, Hofmann wanted to be able to paint full-time. Records of the New York and Provincetown schools are more extensive, but far from complete.